{
  "filename": "2019-2020-HS-History-Bowl-Round-1-A-Set_formattedText.txt",
  "questions": [
    {
      "number": "1.2",
      "quarter": 1,
      "answer": "Crispus Attucks",
      "is_bonus": false,
      "question": "Scholars have conjectured possible relatives of this man based on the fact that his last name means“deer” in Narragansett. This man, who used the alias Michael Johnson, had been a slave of DeaconWilliam Brown. This man’s body lay in state in Faneuil Hall after men under Thomas Preston openedfire on a crowd that had been throwing snowballs. For ten points, name this Native American and AfricanAmerican patriot, the first person killed in the Boston Massacre."
    },
    {
      "number": "1.3",
      "quarter": 1,
      "answer": "(Muhammad) Anwar el-Sadat",
      "is_bonus": false,
      "question": "This ruler broke with the Soviet Union and opened up his economy to the West under his policyof Infitah. Though he had planned the surprise attack Operation Badr, this leader was assassinated byIslamic Jihad because of his diplomatic efforts with Menachem Begin, with whom he shared the 1978Nobel Peace Prize. For ten points, name this successor of Gamal Abdel Nasser as President of Egypt whosigned the Camp David Accords with Israel."
    },
    {
      "number": "1.4",
      "quarter": 1,
      "answer": "circle (accept Black Circle; accept disk) (Note: Legendarily, Giotto was asked by PopeBenedict XI to demonstrate his artistic skill, so he drew a perfect circle with a single motion.)",
      "is_bonus": false,
      "question": "Kazimir Malevich’s 1915 painting of a Black one of these things supported an essay explaining ashift “From Cubism to Suprematism”. Two of these things appear in the background of a Rembrandt selfportrait that may be a reference to a legend about Giotto. One of the earliest works of abstraction, Hilmaaf Klint’s Svanen, is a colorful group of concentric ones of these shapes. Medieval European art frequentlydepicts God creating the world by using a compass to draw, for ten points, what basic, round shape?"
    },
    {
      "number": "1.5",
      "quarter": 1,
      "answer": "Spanish-American War",
      "is_bonus": false,
      "question": "Causes of this war included the execution of the crew of the Virginius. During this war, hundreds ofsoldiers died thanks to Russell Alger’s cut-rate rations in the Embalmed Beef scandal. Frederic Remingtonwas told to furnish pictures so that William Randolph Hearst could furnish this war, which was supportedby yellow journalism. The sinking of the USS Maine helped trigger, for ten points, what war between theUS and a European falling power in 1898?"
    },
    {
      "number": "1.6",
      "quarter": 1,
      "answer": "Detroit Tigers (accept either or both names)Page 1NHBB A-Set Bowl 2019-2020 Bowl Round 1",
      "is_bonus": false,
      "question": "In 1947, this team’s GM Billy Evans wrote “TRUST YOU WILL FIND YOUR NEW CONNECTIONA MOST PROFITABLE ONE” in an antisemitic telegram telling Jewish-American star Hank Greenberghe’d been given away to the Pittsburgh Pirates. In 1912, a player for this team shouted “I don’t care if hegot no feet! ” when fans tried to get him to stop beating a handicapped man who had been heckling him;that player’s career hits record was broken by Pete Rose. The notoriously racist Ty Cobb played over twodecades with, for ten points, what Major League Baseball team in Michigan?"
    },
    {
      "number": "1.7",
      "quarter": 1,
      "answer": "Caligula (accept Gaius Caesar; accept Gaius Julius Caesar Augustus Germanicus;do not prompt on Caesar alone)",
      "is_bonus": false,
      "question": "This man was assassinated by Cassius Chaeraea after attempting to permanently move to Alexandria. This man may have gone mad after the death of Julia Drusilla, leading to rumors that he appointedIncitatus as a state official. This son of Germanicus was affectionately called “little boot” by the legions. Tiberius was succeeded as emperor by, for ten points, what Roman emperor who supposedly made hishorse a consul?"
    },
    {
      "number": "1.8",
      "quarter": 1,
      "answer": "United States of America (or USA; accept America)",
      "is_bonus": false,
      "question": "During a visit to this country, one psychologist stated that his only goal was to “catch sight of aporcupine;” that trip led Sigmund Freud to conclude that this country “was a mistake”. A psychologistfrom this country developed the ideas of habit, will, and stream of consciousness in his book Principlesof Psychology; that man also wrote the book Pragmatism. For ten points, name this home country ofWilliam James, who was a professor at Harvard."
    },
    {
      "number": "1.9",
      "quarter": 1,
      "answer": "Lavender Scare (accept Lavender Lads, the slur by Dirksen; prompt on descriptive answers)",
      "is_bonus": false,
      "question": "Investigations of this event included the Hoey Report, which was criticized by the U.S. Navy’sCrittenden Report. A slur by Everett Dirksen inspired the popular name for this event, in which PresidentEisenhower’s Executive Order 10450 led to numerous firings of “subversives” from the State Department. Roy Cohn was accused of being closeted during, for ten points, what 1950s “scare” regarding homosexualsin the US Government?"
    },
    {
      "number": "1.10",
      "quarter": 1,
      "answer": "Memphis",
      "is_bonus": false,
      "question": "In this city, after the deaths of Echol Cole and Robert Walker in garbage compactors sparked asanitation strike, the Mason Temple became the site of the “I’ve Been to the Mountaintop” speech onApril 3, 1968. The next day at this city’s Lorraine Motel, James Earl Ray shot and killed the oratorof that speech. Martin Luther King Jr. was assassinated in, for ten points, what second-largest city inTennessee?"
    },
    {
      "number": "1.11",
      "quarter": 1,
      "answer": "AlbaniaPage 2NHBB A-Set Bowl 2019-2020 Bowl Round 1",
      "is_bonus": false,
      "question": "This country, the only non-microstate in Europe that did not sign the Helsinki Accords, executeda priest for baptizing a child in 1971, four years after it declared itself the world’s first atheist state. Hundreds of thousands of concrete bunkers were built in this country during the Cold War under EnverHoxha, who replaced King Zog as its leader. For ten points, name this Balkan country where, in 1991,communism fell in Tirana."
    },
    {
      "number": "2.1",
      "quarter": 2,
      "answer": "Benito Pablo Ju´arez Garcia",
      "is_bonus": false,
      "question": "This leader, who defined peace as “respect for the rights of others,” confiscated Catholic Churchland in the Law of the Nationalization of the Ecclesiastical Wealth. This man’s Minister of the Interior,Francisco Zarco, created the rurales, a mounted police force that was expanded by Porfirio Diaz. Thisman’s family fled to New York after an invasion by Maximilian I, but he was restored to power in 1867. For ten points, name this Zapotec president who led the Liberals during the Reform War and opposed theFrench invasion of Mexico."
    },
    {
      "number": "2.1.B",
      "quarter": 2,
      "answer": "Battle of Puebla",
      "is_bonus": true,
      "question": "During Juarez’s presidencey, Ignacio Zaragoza won this May 5, 1862 battle that delayed theFrench takeover of Mexico. This battle is annually commemorated on Cinco de Mayo."
    },
    {
      "number": "2.2",
      "quarter": 2,
      "answer": "Nazi German extermination camps (accept concentration camps; accept equivalents likedeath camps)",
      "is_bonus": false,
      "question": "One of these facilities in Sobibor was demolished after Alexander Pechersky and Leon Feldhendlerorganized a revolt. Methods developed in the Aktion T4 program were used in these facilities. OperationReinhard involved the construction and use of these facilities, where Zyklon B was used; the operationwas named for Reinhard Heydrich. Treblinka, Buchenwald, and Auschwitz were sites of, for ten points,what facilities built by Nazi Germany to carry out the Holocaust?"
    },
    {
      "number": "2.2.B",
      "quarter": 2,
      "answer": "cyanide (accept hydrogen cyanide)",
      "is_bonus": true,
      "question": "The poison gas involved in Zyklon B is based on this compound, which was first isolated fromthe pigment Prussian blue."
    },
    {
      "number": "2.3",
      "quarter": 2,
      "answer": "James Earl “Jimmy” Carter, Jr.",
      "is_bonus": false,
      "question": "This politician published the autobiography Why Not the Best? shortly before declaring to run in theprimary elections. During his term, this President oversaw the evacuation of Love Canal and the passing ofthe Superfund law. This man’s namesake doctrine sanctioned the USSR for their invasion of Afghanistan,and he boycotted the Moscow Summer Olympics shortly before he lost re-election. The 2002 Nobel PeacePrize was awarded to, for ten points, what US President who was succeeded by Ronald Reagan?"
    },
    {
      "number": "2.3.B",
      "quarter": 2,
      "answer": "Habitat for Humanity (International)Page 3NHBB A-Set Bowl 2019-2020 Bowl Round 1",
      "is_bonus": true,
      "question": "Carter and his wife Rosalynn have increased public awareness of this Georgia-based charity thatuses a volunteer labor force to build housing around the world."
    },
    {
      "number": "2.4",
      "quarter": 2,
      "answer": "Palace of Versailles",
      "is_bonus": false,
      "question": "At this location, the Marquis de Lafayette’s willingness to kiss a queen’s hand helped calm tensionsduring the October Days after cannons from the Hotel de Ville were dragged here by angry womenprotesting the price of bread. Charles Le Brun helped supervise the construction of this facility, whichfeatured gardens designed by Andre Le Notre and a Hall of Mirrors. Paris was replaced as the site of theroyal court by, for ten points, what French palace complex built by Louis XIV [14]?"
    },
    {
      "number": "2.4.B",
      "quarter": 2,
      "answer": "Third Estate (accept tiers-´etat; prompt on bourgeoisie; prompt on peasants)",
      "is_bonus": true,
      "question": "The Women’s March on Versailles, or the October Days, was a food riot of this social class. Over90% of France was part of this class; the clergy and nobility held power as the two other classes."
    },
    {
      "number": "2.5",
      "quarter": 2,
      "answer": "United States Postal Service (accept USPS; accept US Mail)",
      "is_bonus": false,
      "question": "This agency changed its policies after an incident involving four year old Charlotte May Pierstorff. In 1970, this agency allowed its workers to be given collective bargaining rights after a nationwide strikeinvolving 210,000 employees. People were forbidden to use this agency for obscene purposes by theComstock Laws. Until 1971, the leader of this agency was a member of the Cabinet. For ten points, namethis government agency for which Ben Franklin served as the first postmaster general."
    },
    {
      "number": "2.5.B",
      "quarter": 2,
      "answer": "they mailed themselves (accept descriptions relating to living people being shipped inthe mail)",
      "is_bonus": true,
      "question": "Charlotte May Pierstorff changed USPS policy by performing this action. Henry “Box” Brownescaped slavery via the Adams Express Company and this process."
    },
    {
      "number": "2.6",
      "quarter": 2,
      "answer": "helots (prompt on descriptions of (Spartan) slaves)",
      "is_bonus": false,
      "question": "A legend relates that these people came into existence after a namesake region revolted against AgisI. People born of these women were labeled as nothoi. An earthquake in the Eurotas Valley allowed thesepeople to launch a revolt. Members of the Krypteia could kill these people without repercussions. Thesesubjugated farmers made up the bulk of the population of ancient Laconia. For ten points, name this classof slaves in Sparta."
    },
    {
      "number": "2.6.B",
      "quarter": 2,
      "answer": "agoge [uh-goh-gay]Page 4NHBB A-Set Bowl 2019-2020 Bowl Round 1",
      "is_bonus": true,
      "question": "Most helots worked as farmers, but some worked as servants in this education system for Spartanboys."
    },
    {
      "number": "2.7",
      "quarter": 2,
      "answer": "Robert Mugabe",
      "is_bonus": false,
      "question": "After land mines and missiles were found at Ascot House, this man dismissed another leader as “acobra in the house”. The Gukhurahundi massacres, whose name means “the early rain that washes awaythe chaff,” were carried out by this leader’s army. In the 2013 elections, this opponent of Joshua Nkomoclaimed he would “fight like a wounded animal”. After sacking Emmerson Mnangagwa, this man wasplaced under house arrest. For ten points, name this leader of Zimbabwe from 1980 to 2017."
    },
    {
      "number": "2.7.B",
      "quarter": 2,
      "answer": "ZANU-PF (accept Zimbabwe African National Union - Patriotic Front; prompt onpartial answers)",
      "is_bonus": true,
      "question": "Mugabe led this Zimbabwean political party, which shared power for the first time in historyin 2008 after Morgan Tsvangirai’s [chang-ee-rai’s] Movement for Democratic Change won 100 seats inparliament."
    },
    {
      "number": "2.8",
      "quarter": 2,
      "answer": "Chernobyl nuclear meltdown (or disaster, etc.)",
      "is_bonus": false,
      "question": "This event led to the resettlement of 18,000 children in the Cuban resort town of Tarara. TheLiquidators group was formed to bulldoze pine trees after this event, which required the building of aconcrete sarcophagus. A high incidence of thyroid cancer was discovered among people in the vicinity ofthis event, which created the Red Forest. Pripyat was evacuated as a result of a failure in reactor 4 during,for ten points, what 1986 nuclear disaster in Soviet Ukraine?"
    },
    {
      "number": "2.8.B",
      "quarter": 2,
      "answer": "glasnost",
      "is_bonus": true,
      "question": "Mikhail Gorbachev advocated for this policy of “openness” in the wake of Chernobyl and otherincidents of Soviet non-transparency."
    },
    {
      "number": "3.1",
      "quarter": 3,
      "answer": "Abigail Adams",
      "is_bonus": false,
      "question": "Wife of John Adams, who advised him “Remember the ladies...”"
    },
    {
      "number": "3.2",
      "quarter": 3,
      "answer": "Martha Washington (prompt on Washington; accept Martha Dandridge)",
      "is_bonus": false,
      "question": "First First Lady of the United States, who oversaw Mount Vernon."
    },
    {
      "number": "3.3",
      "quarter": 3,
      "answer": "Virginia Dare",
      "is_bonus": false,
      "question": "First English child born in the New World; she disappeared with the Roanoke Colony."
    },
    {
      "number": "3.4",
      "quarter": 3,
      "answer": "Elizabeth “Betsy” Ross (accept Elizabeth Griscom; accept Elizabeth Ashburn; acceptElizabeth Claypoole)",
      "is_bonus": false,
      "question": "Seamstress who legendarily made the first American flag."
    },
    {
      "number": "3.5",
      "quarter": 3,
      "answer": "Molly Pitcher (prompt on partial answers)",
      "is_bonus": false,
      "question": "Nickname of a woman, probably Mary Ludwig Hays, who heroically assisted at the Battle ofMonmouth."
    },
    {
      "number": "3.6",
      "quarter": 3,
      "answer": "Phillis Wheatley",
      "is_bonus": false,
      "question": "Freed slave and poet who met “his Excellence, George Washington” in 1776."
    },
    {
      "number": "3.7",
      "quarter": 3,
      "answer": "Margaret “Peggy” Shippen (prompt on “Margaret” and/or “Peggy” and/or “Arnold”)",
      "is_bonus": false,
      "question": "British spy who assisted her husband, Benedict Arnold, in his plot to betray West Point."
    },
    {
      "number": "3.8",
      "quarter": 3,
      "answer": "Mary DyerPage 6NHBB A-Set Bowl 2019-2020 Bowl Round 1Eighty Years’ WarName the...",
      "is_bonus": false,
      "question": "Quaker who was hanged in June 1660 after a brief staged reprieve, becoming the third Boston Martyrto be executed."
    },
    {
      "number": "3.9",
      "quarter": 3,
      "answer": "Spain",
      "is_bonus": false,
      "question": "Empire that held the Netherlands as a personal union prior to the Eighty Years’ War."
    },
    {
      "number": "3.10",
      "quarter": 3,
      "answer": "Habsburgs (accept Hapsburgs)",
      "is_bonus": false,
      "question": "Dynastic house from Austria that, at the time, ruled that country."
    },
    {
      "number": "3.11",
      "quarter": 3,
      "answer": "Holy Roman Empire (accept Sacrum Imperium Romanum; accept Heiliges R¨omischesReich)",
      "is_bonus": false,
      "question": "Largely German empire of which the Netherlands was officially a part until 1648."
    },
    {
      "number": "3.12",
      "quarter": 3,
      "answer": "William I (accept William of Orange; accept William the Silent; accept William theTaciturn; accept Willem de Zwijger; accept Willem van Oranje; prompt on “William”)",
      "is_bonus": false,
      "question": "Leader of the Dutch Revolt, the father of the Netherlands, who was assassinated by Balthasar G´erard."
    },
    {
      "number": "3.13",
      "quarter": 3,
      "answer": "Portugal",
      "is_bonus": false,
      "question": "Kingdom that lost control of the Malabar Coast and the Cape of Good Hope as part of a war withthe Dutch."
    },
    {
      "number": "3.14",
      "quarter": 3,
      "answer": "hellburners (accept hellebranders)",
      "is_bonus": false,
      "question": "Fireships that worked as floating bombs during the Siege of Antwerp; ships of the same name foughtthe Spanish Armada."
    },
    {
      "number": "3.15",
      "quarter": 3,
      "answer": "Peace of Mu¨nster",
      "is_bonus": false,
      "question": "Treaty, part of the larger Peace of Westphalia, that established the Dutch Republic in 1648."
    },
    {
      "number": "3.16",
      "quarter": 3,
      "answer": "Sea Beggars (accept Watergeuzen; accept Gueux de mer)Page 7NHBB A-Set Bowl 2019-2020 Bowl Round 1Modern Asian LeadersName the...",
      "is_bonus": false,
      "question": "Confederation of Dutch nobles led by Willem Bloys van Treslong that seized Brielle after losing accessto British ports."
    },
    {
      "number": "3.17",
      "quarter": 3,
      "answer": "Kim family",
      "is_bonus": false,
      "question": "North Korean family that advocates Juche and includes Supreme Leader Jong-un."
    },
    {
      "number": "3.18",
      "quarter": 3,
      "answer": "Xi [shee] Jinping",
      "is_bonus": false,
      "question": "Leader who announced the One Belt, One Road Initiative as China’s current President."
    },
    {
      "number": "3.19",
      "quarter": 3,
      "answer": "Narendra Modi",
      "is_bonus": false,
      "question": "Successor of Manmohan Singh and BJP party leader who became Prime Minister in 2014."
    },
    {
      "number": "3.20",
      "quarter": 3,
      "answer": "Aung San Suu Kyi [chee]",
      "is_bonus": false,
      "question": "Founder of the National League for Democracy who won the 1991 Nobel Peace Prize under housearrest in Rangoon."
    },
    {
      "number": "3.21",
      "quarter": 3,
      "answer": "Nursultan Abishuly Nazarbayev",
      "is_bonus": false,
      "question": "President who resigned in 2019 and now lends his name to the capital of Kazakhstan."
    },
    {
      "number": "3.22",
      "quarter": 3,
      "answer": "Shinzo Abe",
      "is_bonus": false,
      "question": "Liberal Democratic Prime Minister whose economic policy is based on “three arrows.”"
    },
    {
      "number": "3.23",
      "quarter": 3,
      "answer": "Saad Hariri",
      "is_bonus": false,
      "question": "Lebanese Prime Minister whose father’s 2005 assassination sparked the Cedar Revolution."
    },
    {
      "number": "3.24",
      "quarter": 3,
      "answer": "Wangchuck familyPage 8NHBB A-Set Bowl 2019-2020 Bowl Round 1",
      "is_bonus": false,
      "question": "Ruling family of Bhutan whose “Dragon King” Jigme Singye abdicated in 2006."
    },
    {
      "number": "4.2",
      "quarter": 4,
      "answer": "Duke Ellington (accept Edward Kennedy Ellington)",
      "is_bonus": false,
      "question": "This musician included tracks like “Sonnet for Sister Kate” and “Sonnet for Caesar”in a twelve-part suite based on the work of William Shakespeare. Paul Gonsalves played a27-chorus solo in the middle of “Diminuendo and Crescendo in Blue” at the 1956 Newport(+) Jazz Festival, where this bandleader was begged to stick to a curfew. Juan Tizol andsaxophonist Johnny Hodges played in this man’s orchestra. Billy Strayhorn’s (*) “Take the‘A’ Train” was a theme song of, for ten points, what jazz pianist and composer of “Mood Indigo” and “ItDon’t Mean a Thing (If it Ain’t Got That Swing)” who led the Cotton Club Orchestra?"
    },
    {
      "number": "4.3",
      "quarter": 4,
      "answer": "Andrew Jackson",
      "is_bonus": false,
      "question": "This man, who was accused of cannibalism in the Coffin Handbills, won a battle afterthe opposing soldiers forgot to bring ladders to climb the fortifications that this man hadconstructed. During that battle, this man was assisted by the French (+) pirate JeanLafitte. This man defeated the Creek at Horseshoe Bend, the last battle of the Red StickWar, and he defeated Edward Pakenham in a battle that occurred (*) after the Treaty ofGhent ended the War of 1812. For ten points, name this general who won the Battle of New Orleansbefore being elected President in 1828."
    },
    {
      "number": "4.4",
      "quarter": 4,
      "answer": "Battle of Verdun",
      "is_bonus": false,
      "question": "In this battle, the losing commander devised an attrition strategy known as OperationJudgement. To end this battle, Charles Mangin helped one side recapture a location thatthe losers captured without firing a shot on this battle’s third day, (+) Fort Douaumont. Control of the Meuse Heights was a central goal of Erich Falkenhayn during this battle,which began roughly three months prior to the Battle of the (*) Somme. The German plan to“bleed [the French] white” failed at, for ten points, what longest battle of World War I’s Western Front?"
    },
    {
      "number": "4.5",
      "quarter": 4,
      "answer": "ancient Egypt",
      "is_bonus": false,
      "question": "A god from this civilization was syncretized with Hermes to form Hermes Trismegistus,the purported author of the Hermetic Corpus. While at this civilization’s Siwa (+) oasis,Alexander the Great proclaimed himself to be a god. Worship of the syncretic god Serapisin this civilization was instituted by (*) Ptolemy I, and worship of the sun disk Aten here wasinstituted by Akenaten. For ten points, name this civilization whose people worshiped the pharaohs asincarnations of Osiris and Horus."
    },
    {
      "number": "4.6",
      "quarter": 4,
      "answer": "Toni Morrison (or Chloe Anthony Wofford Morrison)Page 9NHBB A-Set Bowl 2019-2020 Bowl Round 1",
      "is_bonus": false,
      "question": "This author discussed the election of Donald Trump in the essay “Mourning forWhiteness”. This author’s hometown of Lorain, Ohio is the setting of her debut novel,in which marigolds ominously fail to bloom and (+) Pecola longs for the title symbol ofwhiteness. In the aftermath of the Whitewater scandal, this author described Bill Clintonas the first black president. (*) Escaped slave Margaret Garner inspired a novel by this author inwhich a murdered baby returns from the Ohio River as a ghost. For ten points, name this American Nobellaureate who wrote The Bluest Eye and Beloved."
    },
    {
      "number": "4.7",
      "quarter": 4,
      "answer": "William I of England (accept William the Conqueror; accept William the Bastard;accept William of Normandy; prompt on William)",
      "is_bonus": false,
      "question": "This man attempted to secure power by forcing his nobles to swear the Salisbury Oath. This ruler’s suppression of the revolt of Edgar the Aetheling was so destructive that thecampaign became known as the (+) “Harrying of the North”. This man accounted forlandholdings in his territory by ordering the compilation of the (*) Domesday [“doomsday”]Book. The Bayeux Tapestry depicts the death of Harold Godwinson at the hands of this man’s archers. For ten points, name this Norman duke who was crowned King of England after his 1066 victory atHastings."
    },
    {
      "number": "4.8",
      "quarter": 4,
      "answer": "Berlin Airlift",
      "is_bonus": false,
      "question": "A message sent by William Draper to the overseer of this effort included a request for“seventy Dakotas”. After the success of this effort, a parade was thrown in New York Cityto celebrate Lucius (+) Clay. On a day called Black Friday, low visibility conditions saw anabnormal amount of participants in this effort fail to arrive on schedule at (*) Tempelhof. “Raisin bombers” helped improve children’s morale in, for ten points, what American supply effort thatavoided a Soviet blockade of a divided German city?"
    },
    {
      "number": "4.9",
      "quarter": 4,
      "answer": "First Opium War (accept First Anglo-Chinese War)",
      "is_bonus": false,
      "question": "Escalation in tensions before this war included a bombardment ordered by Lord Napierand a seizure of stockpiles by Charles Elliott. As a result of successful operations in thiswar, the name “devil ship” was given to the iron warship (+) Nemesis. During this war,Chusan and the Bogue Forts on the Pearl River Delta were captured. To end this war, the(*) Daoguang Emperor accepted the Treaty of Nanking, granting Hong Kong to Britain. For ten points,name this 1839-42 war in China sparked by the trade of addictive narcotics."
    }
  ],
  "categories": ["Colonial Women", "Eighty Years' War", "Modern Asian Leaders"]

}